this that you see here in the matter of
two months I'm gonna turn it into this
or even this or even this and in the two
months I'm gonna turn these hundred
dollars into a million dollars and I'm
going to show you guys the whole entire
process here on YouTube and on my
Instagram we're gonna Journey every
single trade that I take everything will
be audited in an account that will be
available to everyone to review and
track on your own time I want to be as
transparent as possible with this chat I
make this all much more interesting I
would donate 10 of the profits that it
generate in the two months you guys
would choose the charity if somebody
guesses the exact amount that I finish
by the end of the two months I'm going
to be starting this challenge Monday
July 24th I'll be showing the whole
process on Instagram and then here I'm
going to be breaking down the weekly
progress of the account and why I took
certain trades explain the entries of
all of them and showing the results here
every single Sunday on my YouTube
channel and very excited for this
challenge this shows you guys to never
get comfortable make sure to stay tuned
instead of forget I'll see you guys next
week